Inventory of the Warner T. Jones 1819-1891
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Legal Papers, 1838-1890 (Box 2-8)
  - Thomas E. Johnston administrator of Indiana Johnston vs. Thomas B. Rowe et als. - Suit, 1870., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:312)
  - Catharine E. Jones et als. vs. Benjamin B. Dutton, administrator of Ja[me]s C. Dutton et als. - Suit, 1859., 3 items. (Box-folder 5:313)
  - Richard P. Jones - Accounts, 1833-1883., 160 items. (Box-folder 5:314)
    Including statement of debts and agreement to transfer to creditors a portion of Lands End, an estate in Gloucester County.
  - Walter F. Jones - Suits, 1861-1870., 14 items. (Box-folder 5:315)
    Suits against Walter F. Jones for debt. Note: Walter F. Jones executed trust deeds in 1858 and 1859, covering a tract of land in Gloucester County, called Waverley.
  - Papers of Warner T. Jones, 1839-1889. (Box-folder 5:316-320)
    - Warner T. Jones - Personal accounts, 1839-1888., 225 items, including 2 memorandum books. (Box-folder 5:316)
    - Warner T. Jones - Memoranda on legal cases, 1867, 1868, 1874, and n.d., 4 items. (Box-folder 5:317)
    - Warner T. Jones - Professional accounts, 1842-1853., 4 items. (Box-folder 5:318)
    - Warner T. Jones - Accounts for collection, 1845-1885., 29 items. (Box-folder 5:319)
      Including correspondence.
    - Warner T. Jones - Fee book, 1869-1889., 1 item. (Box-folder 5:320)
      Commissioner in chancery, Gloucester County.
  - William Jones estate, 1847-1853., 36 items. (Box-folder 6:321)
  - Peter Kemp - Receipts, 1849., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:322)
  - William Langborn - Military claim, n.d. (Box-folder 6:323)
  - R.M. Lee - Tax bill, 1853., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:324)
  - Lee & Overly vs. George Fary - Suit, 1854-1857., 4 items. (Box-folder 6:325)
  - William R. Linebough - Estate, 1846-1853., 34 items. (Box-folder 6:326)
    Including accounts of Mrs. Susan Linebough.
  - C. H. Mathias vs. Marcellus J. Williams et als. - Suit, 1851., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:327)
  - [?] McCandlish vs. McCandlish, and Barlow vs. McCandlish et al. - Suits, 1881-1883., 2 items. (Box-folder 6:328)
  - John W. Minor vs. Thomas M. Stubblefield - Suit, 1848., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:329)
  - William Minor vs. John Minor and Ransone White, administrator of James Miller - Suit, 1845., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:330)
  - Thomas S. Oliver - Estate, 1858-1859., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:331)
  - Washington Oliver vs. Edward H. Rowe et als. - Suit, 1868., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:332)
  - Doctor [?] Page - Invoice, 1863., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:333)
    Invoice due W. H. Herbert.
  - John Page and wife, Lucy M. Page, and William T. Burwell to M. B. Seawell - Power of attorney, 1866., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:334)
    Power of attorney for the division of certain property in England.
  - Lucy Ann Page - Accounts and invoices, 1856-1868., 7 items. (Box-folder 6:335)
  - Richard P. Page - Accounts, 1860-1861., 2 items. (Box-folder 6:336)
  - Allen Paine vs. L. S. Stubbs - Suit, 1858., 3 items. (Box-folder 6:337)
  - Portan - Papers concerning a tract of land, 1838-1854., 5 items. (Box-folder 6:338)
    Papers concerning a tract of land in Gloucester County, called Portan
  - Richmond Examiner(newspaper) - Subscriptions, 1863-1864., 3 items. (Box-folder 6:339)
  - Marian M. Robins - Account, 1887-1888., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:340)
    Account with her trustee under the will of William P. Smith.
  - Papers of William Robins, 1843-1854. (Box-folder 6:341-344)
    - William Robins. William S. Field, assignee of William P. Smith, vs. William Robins, Jr., et al. - Suit, 1853-1854., 2 items. (Box-folder 6:341)
    - William Robins - Suit, 1852., 2 items. (Box-folder 6:342)
      James T. Fleming vs. William Robins and Augustine W. Robins. Suit in Gloucester County.
    - William Robins. William Massenburg and James Massenburg vs. William Robins and wife, et al. - Suit, 1854., 12 items. (Box-folder 6:343)
      Suit in Elizabeth City County.
    - William Robins - Fee bills, 1843-1845., 5 items. (Box-folder 6:344)
      Fee bills due to John R. Cary and paid by A. W. Robins.
  - John N. Rose and wife vs. William S. Thurston's executor et al.; and William Nuttall vs. Wyndham Kemp's administrator - Suit, 1875-1890., 7 items. (Box-folder 6:345)
  - Papers of Joshua F. Ross, 1884-1887. (Box-folder 6:346-349)
    - Joshua F. Ross - Suits, 1887., 2 items. (Box-folder 6:346)
      Suits against Joshua F. Ross in Gloucester County.
    - Joshua F. Ross - Abstracts of mortgages, 1884-1885., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:347)
      Abstracts of mortgages given by Joshua F. Ross on a tract of land called Lower White Marsh.
    - Joshua F. Ross. Warwick Brothers vs. J. F. Ross and T. C. Walker - Suit, 1887., 2 items. (Box-folder 6:348)
    - Joshua F. Ross - Invoices and notes, 1885., 3 items. (Box-folder 6:349)
      Invoices and notes of Joshua F. Ross.
  - E. H. Rowe vs. M. B. Seawell, executor, et al. - Suit, 1882., 6 items. (Box-folder 6:350)
  - James Henry Rowe and wife, Ann Maria Rose, to Wyndham Kemp - Indenture, 26 June 1866., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:351)
    Indenture covering a tract of land in Gloucester County.
  - Jasper C. Rowe and William H. Rowe - Suits, 1861., 2 items. (Box-folder 6:352)
    Suits in Gloucester County against Jasper C. Rowe and William H. Rowe for debt.
  - Jasper C. Rowe and William O. Rowe - Suit, 1866., 2 items. (Box-folder 6:353)
    Suite in Gloucester County against Jasper C. Rowe and William O. Rowe.
  - John H. Rowe and William H. Rowe - Suit, 1867-1869., 3 items. (Box-folder 6:354)
    Suits in Gloucester County against John H. Rowe and William H. Rowe for debt.
  - Thomas B. Rowe vs. William C. Booker and George Hibble - Suit, 1843-1844., 2 items. (Box-folder 6:355)
  - William H. Rowe - Suit, 1868- 1870., 9 items. (Box-folder 6:356)
    Suits in Gloucester County against William H. Rowe for debt.
  - Papers of William H. Roy, 1855-1882. (Box-folder 6-7:357-362)
    - William H. Roy estate, Gloucester County - Suit, 1871-1882., 6 items. (Box-folder 6:357)
      George Brewer vs. William H. Roy's executors et al. Suit in Gloucester County.
    - William H. Roy estate, Gloucester County - Suit, 1859., 2 items. (Box-folder 6:358)
      A.D. Saunders & Co. vs. W.T. Taliaferro, executor of William H. Roy.
    - William H. Roy estate, Gloucester County - Suit, 1860-1861., 6 items. (Box-folder 6:359)
      Warner T. Taliaferro, Jr., and Thomas T. Taliaferro, executors of William H. Roy vs. Euphan W. Roy et als. Suit in Mathews County.
    - William H. Roy estate, Gloucester County - Opinion, 1859., 1 item. (Box-folder 6:360)
      Opinion of James Lyons on the will of William H. Roy.
    - William H. Roy estate, Gloucester County - Accounts, including correspondence, 1855-1873., 174 items. (Box-folder 6:361)
    - William H. Roy estate - Account book, 1859-1873., 1 item. 78 pages. 12 1/2" x 8". (Box-folder 7:362)
      Account book of Warner T. Taliaferro, executor, with Mrs. Euphan W. Roy. Gloucester County.
  - Fanny E. Seawell vs. J. Hairston Seawell, administrator of John T. Seawell - Suit, 1882., 2 items. (Box-folder 7:363)
  - J. T. Seawell, assignee, vs. R. B. Jones' administrator - Suit, 1884-1885., 3 items. (Box-folder 7:364)
  - Sentinel, Richmond, Virginia, a newspaper, 1864., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:365)
    Subscription.
  - J. B. Sinclair and wife vs. Norfolk Savings Institution and related suits, including correspondence, 1876-1889., 23 items. (Box-folder 7:366)
  - Mrs. T. L. Sinclair vs. W. B. Browne and R. A. Roane, 1882., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:367)
  - Soles & Laws vs. M. C. Richardson et als. - Suit, 1885., 2 items. (Box-folder 7:368)
  - Stokes & Walker vs. W. D. Williams, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:369)
  - Robert H. and Wade E. Stubblefield - Suit, 1861-1871., 6 items. (Box-folder 7:370)
    Suits against Robert H. and Wade E. Stubblefield for debt. Gloucester County.
  - Wade E. Stubblefield - Tax bill, 1879., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:371)
  - Trust deed and trustee's sale, 1880-1884., 2 items. (Box-folder 7:372)
    Trust deed of Mrs. K. V. Tabb to John Newstead Tabb. Covering a tract of land called Crow 's Point, a part of White Marsh, in Gloucester County. 17 July 1880. 4 pages.
    Advertisement of trustee's sale of Crow's Point. Signed by John N. Tabb. 27 Sept. 1884. 1 page.
  - Philip Tabb and wife et als. vs. George Hughes and wife et als. - Suit, 8 Jan[uar]y 1885., 1 item. 4 pages. (Box-folder 7:373)
  - [?] Taliaferro - Receipt, 1854., 1 item. (Box-folder 7:374)
  - Warner T. Taliaferro estate, 1880-1881., 3 items. (Box-folder 7:375)
  - W[illia]m Taliaferro - Accounts and invoices, 1851-1864., 4 items. (Box-folder 7:376)
  - W[illia]m B. Taliaferro - Accounts, 1845-1847., 4 items. (Box-folder 7:377)
  - James Thomas to Warner T. Jones - Deed of trust, 24 July 1871., 1 item. 1 page. (Box-folder 7:378)
    Deed of trust covering a tract of land in Guinea Neck, Gl[oucester] Co[unty], and a schooner called the Samuel C. Hulse.
  - Levi Thomas estate, 1860-1883., 21 items. (Box-folder 7:379)
  - John C. Tomkies estate, 1845-1846., 1 item. 1 page. (Box-folder 7:380)
  - Benjamin G. Tompkins - Suits, 1852., 1 item. 3 pages. (Box-folder 7:381)
    Benjamin G. Tompkins, executor of Elizabeth P. Tompkins vs. Maria B. Tompkins et als; and Henry W. Tabb et al. vs. John W. Jarvis, administrator of Elizabeth P. Tompkins. Suits in Mathews County.
  - Papers of Warner Hall, an estate in Gloucester County 1873-1889. (Box-folder 7-8:382-389)
    - Warner Hall, an estate in Gloucester County - Correspondence, 1874-1887., 70 items. (Box-folder 7:382)
      Correspondence of Maxwell T. Clarke with Warner T. Jones.
    - Warner Hall, an estate in Gloucester County - Papers, 1874-1889., 62 items. (Box-folder 8:383)
      Papers relating to the lease of Warner Hall.
    - Warner Hall, an estate in Gloucester County - Papers, 1875-1878., 20 items. (Box-folder 8:384)
      Papers relating to the sale of timber from Warner Hall.
    - Warner Hall, an estate in Gloucester County - Maintenance, 1874-1886., 43 items. (Box-folder 8:385)
      Lumber and other materials used for the maintenance of Warner Hall.
    - Warner Hall, an estate in Gloucester County - Tax bills and memoranda, 1874-1884., 9 items. (Box-folder 8:386)
    - Warner Hall, an estate in Gloucester County - Accounts of Fanny Gardner, a former slave. 1877-1885., 8 items. (Box-folder 8:387)
    - Warner Hall, an estate in Gloucester County - Farm accounts and correspondence, 1879-1885., 8 items. (Box-folder 8:388)
    - Warner Hall, an estate in Gloucester County - Miscellaneous accounts and memoranda, 1873-1887., 14 items. (Box-folder 8:389)
  - William E. Wiatt - Accounts and invoices, 1851-1853., 5 items. (Box-folder 8:390)
  - Papers of the Archibald Willey estate, 1866-1890. (Box-folder 8:391-393)
    - Archibald Willey estate - Account book, 1874-1884., 1 item. (Box-folder 8:391)
      Accounts of estate of Archibald Willey with Sterling Rowe, administrator of estate, and accounts of four Willey children with Warner T. Jones, receiver, and Sterling Rowe, guardian. Volume includes accounts of Carrington & Clark with Warner T. Jones.
    - Archibald Willey estate in Gloucester County - Account book, 1882-1889., 1 item. (Box-folder 8:392)
      Account book containing accounts of Willey children: Odavia E. Willey, Thomas F. Willey, and Archibald H. Willey with Warner T. Jones, receiver.
    - Archibald Willey estate in Gloucester County - Accounts and correspondence, 1866-1890., 28 items. (Box-folder 8:393)
  - Gilderoy Williams - Criminal Suit, 18 May 1850., 1 item. (Box-folder 8:394)
    Commonwealth of Virginia vs. Gilderoy Williams. Criminal suit in Gloucester County.
  - John Williams - Criminal Suit, 18 May 1850., 1 item. (Box-folder 8:395)
    Commonwealth of Virginia vs. John Williams. Criminal suit in Gloucester County.
  - Seth Williams guardianship, 1859-1866., 1 item. (Box-folder 8:396)
  - Mary D. Wright estate, 1846-1847., 11 items. (Box-folder 8:397)
  Series 3:Miscellaneous
- Miscellaneous, 1851-1888. (Box 8:398-399)
  - Miscellaneous papers. 1851-1888., 6 items. (Box-folder 8:398)
  - List of white and colored teachers by counties, For year ending 31 July 1887., 1 item. 1 page. Ms. (Box-folder 8:399)